theshillongtimes.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy – The Shillong Times

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which The Shillong Times collects, uses, display, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [http://www.theshillongtimes.com](http://www.theshillongtimes.com/) website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by The Shillong Times.

**Comments disclaimer**

The Shillong Times allows readers to post comments to almost all our online content. But that doesn’t give you the right to abuse this facility.

We will not delete comments based on their political or ideological viewpoint. We may, however, delete comments that are off-topic, use excessive foul language, or employ slurs based on race, gender, religion, or sexual orientation. We may also delete comments that make personal attacks on story subjects — especially if those attacks are threatening, unrelated to the content of the piece or are unsupported by factual evidence. If you want to use the internet to settle personal scores, you might want to try starting your own blog.

The fact that a comment remains on the site does not imply the endorsement of The Shillong Times. The Shillong Times makes no representation as to the accuracy of any assertions made in the comments section. The Shillong Times assumes no liability for any statements made by third parties in the comments sections of its Web site.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

The Shillong Times may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service  Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  *  To send periodic emails We may use the email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third-parties and Opt-Out**  
Third-parties may display interest-based advertising to you in applications or websites, based on your use of applications or websites over time and across non-affiliated apps.  
Such third-parties may combine and use information from websites or applications on your current browser or device with information from your other browsers or devices for advertising purposes. To opt-out of such interest-based advertising and/or cross-device targeting, please use the methods provided below for opting out on each of your browsers and on each of your devices:  
Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) – http://optout.networkadvertising.org/  
Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) – http://www.aboutads.info/choices/  
Digital Advertising Alliance Canada (DAAC) – http://youradchoices.ca/choices  
Digital Advertising Alliance EU (EDAA) – http://www.youronlinechoices.com/  
Please note that opting out of interest-based advertising and cross-device targeting does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the third-party from which you have opted out of receiving interest-based advertising or cross-device targeting by using the methods provided above will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns on a particular web browser or device.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Changes to this privacy policy**

The Shillong Times has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

##### [The Shillong Times](http://www.theshillongtimes.com/)

#### THE SHILLONG TIMES Pvt Ltd,  
Rilbong, Shillong-4.  
Meghalaya, India

##### 91(0364) 2223488, 2227488 (Shillong). 91(03651) 222526, 222825 (Tura).

letters@theshillongtimes.com

This document was last updated on June 09, 2013
